[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following butterflies mentioned in the reading was the focus of a study in England?",
        "answer": "the British Swallowtail"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following butterflies is known for being attracted to alcohol?",
        "answer": "the Formosan Deadleaf"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the reading, butterflies who fly longer distances in search of food plants are known as _____, and they may actually increase in numbers as a result of climate change.",
        "answer": "generalists"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the reading, the Quino Checkerspot butterfly has had a difficult time migrating (遷徙) around which American city?",
        "answer": "Los Angeles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moths and butterflies are considered to be poikilothermic. This means they are _____.",
        "answer": "cold-blooded"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the reading, the period of time after the Industrial Revolution (工業革命) through the present is known as the _____.",
        "answer": "Anthropocene"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following butterflies is NOT found in Taiwan?",
        "answer": "the Western Monarch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the sientific name for moths and butterflies?",
        "answer": "Lepidopterans"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the reading, climate change is causing some butterflies to become _____.",
        "answer": "smaller"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are butterflies considered an indicator species?",
        "answer": "Because they have been studied in more detail than other insects, and they are quite sensitive to their surroundings."
    }
]